**PRIVACY POLICY**

\_\_\_\_\_\_

Hey there! Welcome to Match’s Privacy Policy.

We know reading a privacy policy might not be everyone’s idea of a good time, but hear us out. We put a lot of effort into making this policy as clear and engaging as possible, because we actually want you to read it! Think of us as your digital wingmate, here to guide you through the ins and outs of what data we collect, and why and how we use it. So get cozy, grab your favorite drink , and let’s make privacy make sense – together.

This Privacy Policy applies from 01/02/2026. The previous version, available [here](https://uk.match.com/pages/misc/privacy_012026), applies until then.

1.  [Who We Are](#CH1)
2.  [Where This Privacy Policy Applies](#CH2)
3.  [Data We Collect](#CH3)
4.  [How We Use Data](#CH4)
5.  [How We Share Data](#CH5)
6.  [How Match Group Companies Work Together](#CH6)
7.  [Cross-Border Data Transfers](#CH7)
8.  [Your Rights](#CH8)
9.  [How Long We Retain Your Data](#CH9)
10.  [Children’s Privacy](#CH10)
11.  [Privacy Policy Changes](#CH11)
12.  [How To Contact Us](#CH12)

### 1\. Who We Are

The company responsible for your data (the “data controller”) is:

Meetic S.A.S.  
MATCH  
53 rue de Châteaudun Paris 9 France

### 2\. Where This Privacy Policy Applies

This Privacy Policy applies to websites, apps, events and other services we operate under the Match brand. Whether you’re searching for your soulmate, joining us at one of our events, or using any of our other awesome services, this Policy has got you covered. For simplicity, we just refer to all of these as our “service” in this Privacy Policy.

If for some reason, one of our services requires its own separate privacy policy, then that policy will be made available to you and that policy—not this Privacy Policy—will apply.

### 3\. Data We Collect

It goes without saying, we can’t help you develop meaningful connections without you providing some information about yourself, like basic profile details and the types of people you’d like to meet. Using our service also generates some information, such as when you logged in and how you used the service, as well as the insights and inferences we generate based on the content you provide. We also collect data from third parties, like when you access the service through an account you have on another platform (e.g., Facebook, Google or Apple) or when you upload information from your account on another platform to complete your profile. If you’re interested in all the details, be sure to check out the table below.

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Data you give us |     |
| Categories | Description |
| Account Data | When you create an account, you give us basic information for your account to be set up such as your phone number, email address, and date of birth. |
| Profile Data | When you complete your profile, you share additional details about you, such as your gender, interests, preferences, approximate location, etc. Some of this data may be considered sensitive or special in certain countries, such as details about sexual orientation, sexual life, health, or political beliefs. If you choose to provide this data, you consent to us using it as laid out in this Privacy Policy. |
| Content | When you use our service, you share photos, videos, audio, text and other types of content, such as your chats with other members. |
| Purchase Data | When you make a purchase or request a refund we keep the details of the transaction (e.g., what you purchased, the date of the transaction, and the price). The exact data depends on the payment method you choose. When you pay directly with us (rather than through a platform such as iOS or Android), you provide your debit or credit card number or other financial information. |
| Marketing, Survey and Research Data | We sometimes run (i) surveys, focus groups, or market studies for research purposes and (ii) promotions, events or contests for marketing purposes. When you choose to participate, you give us information to process your entry and participation, as well as your responses to our questions and your feedback. |
| Third-Party Data | When you choose to share information about other people (for example, if you use the contact details of someone you know for a given feature, or if you submit a query or report involving a member), we process this data on your behalf to complete your request. |
| Customer Support Data | When you contact us, you provide us with information that is necessary to help address your inquiry. Other people can also submit queries or reports involving you. Finally, our moderation tools and teams collect additional data as part of their investigations.<br><br>Further, we are part of the [Match Group family of businesses](https://mtch.com/ourcompany). Match Group considers the safety and security of members a top priority. If you were banned from another Match Group service, your data can be shared with us to allow us to take necessary actions, including closing your account or preventing you from creating an account on our service.<br><br>Where legally allowed, we also receive information about suspected or confirmed bad actors from third parties as part of our efforts to ensure our members’ safety and security. |
| Social Media Data | You can share data with us through your accounts on other platforms (e.g., Facebook, Instagram, Spotify, Apple), for instance if you decide to create and log into your account via these platforms or if you decide to upload data such as photos or playlists onto our service from these platforms. |

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Data generated or automatically collected |     |
| Categories | Description |
| Usage Data | Using the service generates data about your activity, including how you use it (e.g., when you logged in, features you’ve been using, actions taken, information shown to you, referring webpages, ads you interacted with) and how you interact with others (e.g., searching, matching, communicating). We also receive data related to interactions you have with our ads on third party websites or apps, if applicable. |
| Technical Data | Using the service involves the collection of data from and about the device(s) you use to access our service, including hardware and software information such as IP address, device ID, device type, operating system and configurations, network information, as well as app settings and characteristics, app crashes, advertising IDs and identifiers associated with cookies or other technologies that can uniquely identify a device or browser. For more information about cookies, see our [Cookie Policy](https://uk.match.com/pages/misc/cookie?styled=1). |
| Insights and Inferences | Using the service involves the generation of insights and inferences, drawn from your interactions and the information and content you provide, reflecting, e.g., your preferences, characteristics, predispositions, behavior, and attitudes. |

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Other data we collect |     |
| Categories | Description |
| Geolocation Data | If you give us permission, we can collect your geolocation (latitude and longitude) from your device. If you decline permission, certain features that rely on precise geolocation will not be available to you. |
| Face Data | You may choose to participate in certain of our features like Photo Verification, that involve the collection of face data, which is considered biometric data in some jurisdictions. [Learn more about our verification featureand how we process your face data](https://uk.match.com/faq/?answer=0309_ProfileVerifiedPhoto). |
| ID Data | You may choose to provide us with a copy of your government-issued ID to help us check that you’re who you say you are. |

### 4\. Why and How We Use Your Data

The main reason we process your data is to provide our service to you and improve it over time. That includes connecting you with members who might make your heart skip a beat, personalizing your experience, and just helping you make the most of our service. We also process your data to keep our service, you, and others safe and secure. We take this responsibility very seriously, and we’re always working to improve the safety and security of our systems and processes. And yes, we process your data to show relevant ads – you can control this in your settings. Read on for a more detailed explanation.

For information on how we process personal data through “profiling” and “automated decision-making”, please see our [FAQ](https://uk.match.com/faq/?answer=0262_ProfilagePriseDecisionAutomatisee).

|     |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- |
| Purposes for processing your data | Grounds for processing your data | Categories of data processed<br><br>(Those are described in Section 3 of this Policy) |
| To enable you to use our service, including:<br><br>*   Creating and maintaining your account and profile on our service<br>*   Operating and maintaining the various features on our service<br>*   Recommending other members to you and recommending you to them<br>*   Organizing sweepstakes and contests<br>*   Responding to your requests and questions<br>*   Monitoring the well functioning of our service and troubleshooting and fixing issues as needed<br>*   Processing your applications to join one of our premiere/VIP services | *   Performance of our contract with you<br>*   Your consent (where sensitive data or other type of data that requires consent is processed) | *   Account Data<br>*   Profile Data<br>*   Content<br>*   Purchase Data<br>*   Marketing, Survey and Research Data<br>*   Third Party Data<br>*   Customer Support Data<br>*   Social Media Data<br>*   Usage Data<br>*   Technical Data<br>*   Insights and Inferences<br>*   Geolocation Data<br>*   Face Data |
| To enable your purchases on our service, including:<br><br>*   Processing payments and refunds<br>*   Offering discounts and promotions, customizing prices | *   Performance of our contract with you<br>*   Our legitimate interest: it is in our legitimate interest to offer discounts and promotions and customize prices, where and as legally permissible | *   Account Data<br>*   Profile Data<br>*   Technical Data<br>*   Purchase Data<br>*   Usage Data<br>*   Insights and Inferences |
| To operate advertising and marketing campaigns, including:<br><br>*   Performing and measuring the effectiveness of advertising campaigns run on our service<br>*   Performing and measuring the effectiveness of marketing campaigns promoting our own service on third-party platforms<br>*   Communicating with you about products and services we believe may interest you | *   Consent (where required under applicable law) and otherwise our legitimate interest. It is in our legitimate interest to promote our service and to show ads to our members which are tailored to their interests, as a way to improve their experience and help fund the parts of our service which are free | *   Account Data<br>*   Profile Data<br>*   Usage Data<br>*   Marketing, Survey and Research Data<br>*   Technical Data<br>*   Insights and Inferences |
| To improve our service and create new features and services, including:<br><br>*   Running focus groups, market studies and surveys<br>*   Analyzing how our service is used<br>*   Reviewing interactions with customer care teams to improve service quality<br>*   Developing and improving new features and services, including through machine learning and other technologies, and testing them out<br><br>*   Conducting research and publishing research papers | *   Performance of our contract with you<br>*   Our legitimate interest: It is in our legitimate interest to improve our service over time<br>*   Consent where required under applicable law (e.g., we may process data deemed sensitive or special in certain countries to help make sure that the various communities using our service are being treated fairly and equitably and that our service remains diverse and inclusive) | *   Account Data<br>*   Profile Data<br>*   Content<br>*   Purchase Data<br>*   Marketing, Survey and Research Data<br>*   Third Party Data<br>*   Customer Support Data<br>*   Social Media Data<br>*   Usage Data<br>*   Technical Data<br>*   Insights and Inferences |
| To keep you and other members safe on our service and across Match Group, including:<br><br>*   Preventing, detecting and fighting against violations of our [Terms](https://uk.match.com/pages/misc/terms?styled=1) fraud and other illegal or unauthorized activities<br>*   Developing and improving tools to prevent, detect and fight against violations of our Terms, fraud and other illegal or unauthorized activities<br>*   Preventing recurrences, notably by preventing individuals who violate our Terms from creating a new account<br>*   Letting individuals know what we’ve done about reports they submit or potential safety risks we identify<br>*   Verifying your identity<br>*   Securing payments and fighting against financial fraud<br><br>For more information on safety, integrity and security generally, visit our [Safety Tips](https://uk.match.com/safety/) and [Community Guidelines](https://uk.match.com/pages/misc/community-guidelines?styled=1). | *   Performance of our contract with you<br>*   Our legitimate interest: It is in our legitimate interest and that of our members to keep them safe<br>*   Protection of your vital interests and that of other members<br>*   Compliance with legal obligations that apply to us, such as taking down illicit content or notifying users who have interacted with a user whose account is banned<br>*   The processing is necessary for the protection of substantial public interest: it is in the substantial public interest that we prevent, detect and fight against illegal activities on and off our platforms and cooperate with law enforcement authorities on such matters<br><br>*   Your consent (where sensitive data or another type of data that requires consent is processed) | *   Account Data<br>*   Profile Data<br>*   Content<br>*   Purchase Data<br>*   Third Party Data<br>*   Customer Support Data<br>*   Usage Data<br>*   Technical Data<br>*   Face Data<br>*   ID Data<br>*   Insights and Inferences |
| To comply with applicable law, establish, exercise and defend legal claims & rights, including:<br><br>*   Preserving data to comply – and evidence compliance – with applicable law<br>*   Supporting investigations and defending potential or ongoing litigation, regulatory action or dispute<br>*   Responding to lawful requests from law enforcement, courts, regulators, and other third parties<br>*   Reporting illegal or infringing content to law enforcement, government or other authorities<br>*   Establishing, exercising, or defending ongoing or threatened claims<br><br>*   Sharing data with law enforcement or partners to combat abusive or illegal behavior | *   Our legitimate interest: It is in our legitimate interest to comply with applicable law and protect ourselves, our members and others, including as part of investigations, legal proceedings and other disputes<br>*   Protection of your vital interests and that of other members<br>*   Compliance with legal obligations applying to us such as responding to law enforcement requests for information | The categories of data shared will vary based on the specific circumstances surrounding each obligation, compelling interest or dispute |

### 5\. How We Share Data

Since our goal is to help you make meaningful connections, some of your information is of course visible to other members on the service. We also share data with service providers and partners who assist us in operating the service, with other Match Group companies for the reasons laid out below and, in some cases, for legal and related reasons. Read on for more details.

|     |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- |
| Recipients | Reasons for sharing | Categories of Personal Data |
| Other members | You share data with other members when you voluntarily disclose information on the service for others to see (e.g., your public profile).<br><br>If someone submits a report involving you (such as a claim you violated our Terms of Use), we may let the reporter know what actions we took, if any, as a result of their report. The same applies if you submit a report involving another member. | *   Profile Data<br>*   Content<br>*   Social Media Data<br>*   Third Party Data<br>*   Customer Support Data<br>*   Usage Data<br>*   Insights and Inferences |
| Service providers/partners | We share data with vendors and partners who help us operate, promote and improve our service. They provide us services such as data hosting and maintenance, analytics, customer care, marketing, advertising, payment, refund \[and cash out\] processing, legal support, and security operations.<br><br>Specifically, we may use Facebook tools, such as Facebook Login, Pixel, Social plugins, and Facebook SDK for App Events. When using these tools we are considered “Joint Data Controllers” with Meta Ireland. To learn more about how Facebook processes your data and allows you to exercise your rights, check out Meta Ireland’s [Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/privacy/policy).<br><br>Where permitted by applicable law, we may also share data with partners (such as companies facing similar threats), and they may share data with us, when necessary to promote the safety, security, and integrity of our service, our Members, our employees, and others. | Depending on the service provided by the vendor or partner, it may include:<br><br>*   Account Data<br>*   Profile Data<br>*   Content<br>*   Purchase Data<br>*   Marketing, Survey and Research Data<br>*   Third Party Data<br>*   Customer Support Data<br>*   Social Media Data<br>*   Usage Data<br>*   Technical Data<br>*   Insights and Inferences<br>*   Geolocation Data<br>*   Face Data<br>*   ID Data |
| Advertising partners | We publish ads about third-party advertisers’ products and services on our service, and publish ads promoting our own service on third-party sites and apps. To help improve the relevance of these ads, we provide certain info about you to third parties, including advertising partners, or allow them to collect such data from our services (such as via cookies, SDKs, or similar technologies). Some of our advertising partners enable us to transform your email address, advertising identifiers or phone number into an identifier that can’t be used to identify you personally and then use that unique identifier to either exclude you from our marketing campaigns, or to target our ads at an audience that is similar to you in terms of background, interests or app usage. | *   Account Data<br>*   Profile Data<br>*   Usage Data<br>*   Technical Data<br>*   Insights and Inferences |
| Affiliates | We share data with affiliates or receive data from them for the purposes laid out in Section 6 of this policy. | The categories of data will vary based on the reason for sharing, but it may include:.<br><br>*   Account Data<br>*   Profile Data<br>*   Content<br>*   Purchase Data<br>*   Marketing, Survey and Research Data<br>*   Third Party Data<br>*   Customer Support Data<br>*   Social Media Data<br>*   Usage Data<br>*   Technical Data<br>*   Insights and Inferences<br>*   Geolocation Data<br>*   Face Data<br>*   ID Data |
| Law enforcement authorities | We may disclose your data to: (i) comply with a legal process, such as a court order, subpoena or search warrant, government / law enforcement investigation or other legal requirements; (ii) assist in the prevention or detection of crime; (iii) protect the safety of any person; and (iv) establish, exercise or defend legal claims. | The categories of data shared will vary depending on the specific circumstances surrounding the request, but it often can include:<br><br>*   Account data<br>*   Profile Data<br>*   Content<br>*   Purchase Data<br>*   Customer Support Data<br>*   Third Party Data<br>*   Social Media Data<br>*   Usage Data<br>*   Technical Data<br>*   Insights and Inferences<br>*   Geolocation Data<br>*   ID Data |
| In the context of merger and acquisition, with our Affiliates or new owner(s) | We may transfer your data if we are involved, whether in whole or in part, in a merger, sale, acquisition, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, bankruptcy or other change of ownership or control. | The categories of data shared will vary based on the type of corporate transaction. It may include the entire organization data or only a specific subset such as Purchase Data. |
| When the profile sharing functionality is used | You may choose to share other members’ profiles and they may share yours with people outside of our service, using the sharing functionality. | *   Profile Data<br>*   Content |

### 6\. How Match Group Companies Work Together

Match is part of the [Match Group family of businesses](https://mtch.com/ourcompany).

We share data about you with our Affiliates and they share data about you with us, for the reasons laid out below:

*   To make all Match Group platforms safer, for instance by searching for and identifying bad actors and how they operate across Match Group platforms, as well as making sure that when a bad actor is found on one Match Group platform (for instance ours), they can be banned from all.
*   To assist each other, as service providers, in data processing operations, such as data hosting and maintenance, customer care, marketing and targeted advertising, analytics, machine learning development and implementation, finance and accounting, legal support, payment processing, service improvement, data security and fighting against spam, abuse, fraud and other wrongdoings.
*   To suggest to you relevant and meaningful connections, by developing or improving Match Group Brands’ core recommendation systems.
*   To improve your chances at building significant connections with others, we may make you visible on other Match Group services or allow you to benefit from cross-platform functionalities.
*   Where and as allowed under applicable law, to better understand how people use Match Group services overall, to personalize your experience across Match Group services and to enhance marketing and advertising campaigns.
*   For other legitimate business purposes including corporate / consolidated audit, analysis and reporting.

[Learn more](https://uk.match.com/faq/?answer=0332_DataAcrossMG) about how Match Group companies work together.

### 7\. Cross-Border Data Transfers

Because we operate a global service, the sharing of your data laid out in Section 5 involves cross-border data transfers to our Affiliates and service providers (other third parties) in third countries that have different privacy laws. When we transfer personal data to a third-country we use appropriate mechanisms. For example, we rely on:

*   Adequacy decisions issued by the [European Commission](https://commission.europa.eu/law/law-topic/data-protection/international-dimension-data-protection/adequacy-decisions_en) or other competent authorities under applicable laws. We transfer personal data to our Affiliates to perform important functions, as outlined in Section 6, by storing, accessing or otherwise processing data and to third-parties in countries with adequacy decisions for the purposes outlined in Section 5.
*   [Standard contractual clauses](https://ec.europa.eu/info/law/law-topic/data-protection/international-dimension-data-protection/standard-contractual-clauses-scc_en) issued by the European Commission or similar contractual data transfer mechanisms approved by other competent authorities under applicable laws. These contractual data transfer mechanisms are commitments between companies transferring personal data, binding them to protect the confidentiality and security of your data and ensuring adequate level of protection in third countries. We rely on such mechanisms to transfer personal data to our Affiliates to perform important functions, as outlined in Section 6, by storing, accessing or otherwise processing data, and to third parties for the purposes outlined in Section 5 in countries without adequacy decisions, such as the United States of America. [Contact us](https://uk.match.com/faq/#privacyRequest) for a copy.

### 8\. Your Rights

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Your Rights | How to exercise it |
| Access, Portability or To Know<br><br>Right to be informed of the personal data we process about you and/or ask for a copy of it | You can access and review some data directly by logging into your account. You can also retrieve a copy of your data by following the process explained [here](https://uk.match.com/faq/#privacyRequest). |
| Rectification or Correction<br><br>Right to amend or update your personal data where it’s inaccurate or incomplete | You can update your data directly within the service by simply updating your profile. If you wish to rectify other data, please contact us [here](https://uk.match.com/faq/#privacyRequest). |
| Deletion or Erasure<br><br>Right to delete personal data | You can delete some of the data you provided us directly within the service. You can also close your account as explained [here](https://uk.match.com/faq/?answer=0009_Unsubscription) and we’ll delete your data as laid out in this Privacy Policy. In any event, you can always contact us [here](https://uk.match.com/faq/#privacyRequest). |
| Objection (Opt-out) or Restriction<br><br>Right to object to us processing personal data or to request that we temporarily or permanently stop processing personal data | You can directly opt-out from certain of your personal data processing in your account settings. Otherwise you can contact us [here](https://uk.match.com/faq/#privacyRequest) should you wish to object to or restrict a data processing we’ve listed throughout this Privacy Policy. |
| Consent Withdrawal  <br>Right to withdraw a consent you’ve given us to process your personal data for a specific purpose | You can directly withdraw consent you’ve given us either by updating your account settings or removing Device Permissions you’ve agreed to in your device settings (e.g., access to specific types of device data such as phone contacts, photospictures, advertising identifiers and location services, or consent to receive push notifications). When you withdraw consent, certain services may lose functionality. You can always contact us [here](https://uk.match.com/faq/#privacyRequest) for more information. |

We want you to be in control of your data, so we want to remind you of the following rights, options and tools available to you. Depending on where you live, these rights may not apply to you or they may be named differently. If you have any questions on your rights and how to exercise them, please contact us [here](https://uk.match.com/faq/#privacyRequest).

For your protection and the protection of all of our members, we may ask you for information to verify your identity or authority to act on behalf of a member before we can answer the above requests. We wouldn’t want someone else to get in control of your data!

Keep in mind, we can reject requests, including if we are unable to authenticate you, if the request is unlawful or invalid, or if it could infringe on trade secrets or intellectual property or the privacy or other rights of someone else. If you wish to receive information relating to another member, the other member will have to make a request themselves.

In certain countries, including in the European Economic Area and the United Kingdom, you have a right to a judicial remedy and to lodge a complaint with the appropriate data protection authority if you have concerns about how we process your personal data. You can find information about your data protection regulator in the European Economic Area [here](https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members_en), and in the United Kingdom [here](https://ico.org.uk/). The data protection authority you can lodge a complaint with can be that of your habitual residence, where you work or where an alleged infringement took place.

### 9\. How Long We Retain Your Data

We want the connections you make through our service to last forever, but we keep your personal data only as long as necessary for legitimate business reasons (as laid out in Section 4) and as permitted by applicable law.

If you decide to stop using our service, you can close your account and your profile will no longer be visible to other members. Note that we will close your account automatically if you are inactive for two years.

Following account closure, we delete your data as laid out below:

1.  To protect the safety and security of our members, we implement a safety retention window of three months following account closure. During this period, we keep your data to investigate unlawful or harmful conducts. The retention of data during this safety retention window is based on our legitimate interest as well as that of potential third-party victims.
2.  We maintain limited data to comply with legal data retention obligations: in particular, we keep transaction data for 10 years to comply with tax and accounting legal requirements, credit card information for the duration the user can challenge the transaction, and “traffic data” / logs for one year to comply with legal data retention obligations. We also keep records of consents members give us for five years to comply and evidence our compliance with applicable law.
3.  We maintain limited data on the basis of our legitimate interest: we keep user generated content associated with banned account for two years; customer care records and supporting data for six years from the date of the communication, imprecise location of download/purchase for five years in support of our safety efforts, to support our customer care decisions, enforce our rights and enable us to defend ourselves in the event of a claim; profile data for one year in anticipation of potential litigation, for the establishment, exercise or defense of legal claims; and data necessary to prevent members who were banned from opening a new account for as long as necessary to ensure the safety and vital interests of our members.
4.  Finally, we maintain data on the basis of our legitimate interest where there is an outstanding or potential issue, claim or dispute requiring us to keep data, in particular if we receive a valid legal subpoena or request asking us to preserve data (in which case we would need to keep the data to comply with our legal obligations) or if data would otherwise be necessary as part of legal proceedings.

Where appropriate and as legally permitted, we may maintain and use data that, by itself, cannot identify or be attributed specifically to you for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy, including to improve our service and create new features, technologies and services, including through machine learning, and keep Match Group services safe.

### 10\. Children’s Privacy

Our service is restricted to individuals who are 18 years of age or older. We do not permit individuals under the age of 18 on our platform. If you suspect that a member is under the age of 18, please use the reporting mechanism available on the service.

### 11\. Privacy Policy Changes

This policy will change over time. We’re always looking for new and innovative ways to help you build meaningful connections and strive to make sure explanations of our data practices remain up-to-date. We will notify you before material changes take effect so that you have time to review the changes.

### 12\. How to Contact Us

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy or would like to make a complaint, you have different options below:

#### If you live in the European Economic Area:

Online: [here](https://uk.match.com/faq/#privacyRequest)

By post:

Data Protection Officer

Meetic SAS  
Match  
53 rue de Châteaudun Paris 9 FRANCE

For more information on how to contact the data protection officer, please click [here](https://uk.match.com/faq/#privacyRequest)

#### If you live in the United Kingdom:

Online: [here](mailto:rep_matchuk@prighter.com)

By post:

Prighter Group  
20 Mortlake High Street  
London, SW14 8JN,  
United Kingdom

UK representation certificate and representative details [here](https://app.prighter.com/portal/11742804131)

Well, that’s it! You’ve made it to the end of our Privacy Policy. We hope it was as engaging and clear as we tried to make it. Now, let’s get out there and start making some memories! We’re excited to be on this journey with you.
